I said give me a juice, but I won't take it.
[Music]
Jumperme bumper,
here's what I put here, how much is
that 1 rupee, brother, brother, I
didn't take that much from the shop, brother, I
took a juice.
What is the price of sugar for me?
Brother, why don't you put jaggery on me because of the sugar?
Here is 250 rupees on the jaggery. Brother, what's the
matter? Pirikeda,
how much has the sugar increased? I urgently need to
go to the house and tell you that I have left sugar in the tea.
My phone, what is my phone? Yes, you put it there, brother, did you see
my phone? No, I didn't see it. Brother, please
remember a little better.
Brother,
that second, our shop
was on the highway, where 20 people come. He said, "You can't have your phone with you." Brother, "
Okay, your phone." He said, "My uncle is a
policeman." He called him. "
Whatever you do today,
this is
your life, your life."